<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<product>
	<title>NO MORE ROOM IN HELL</title>
	<release-dates>
		<release-date>itch.io - 14 Jun, 2022</release-date>		
	</release-dates>

	<website>http://diegogiacomelli.com.br/games/no-more-room-in-hell</website>	

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>itch.io</name>
			<link>https://giacomelli.itch.io/no-more-room-in-hell</link>
		</platform>	
	</platforms>
	
	<prices>
		<price>
			<currency></currency>
			<value>Free</value>
		</price>
   	</prices>


	<description>
	A 2D top-down survival shooter game where you will be a rookie soldier in a secret government laboratory when a zombie apocalypse started out of blue and now you need to find your way to the docks to have a chance to be your wife and son again.

	The player starts with a very small inventory and alongside the game a better outfit with an even bigger inventory can be found and you will need its whole space to store the 7 different weapons, painkillers, maps, walkman, and music available during the 4 levels.

	You can use a map, surveillance monitor, and cameras that allow you to find your mission targets to finish the levels.

	Besides all this, you can make your way by exploding and shooting walls, because a lot of the game scenarios are fully destructible, and, of course, you will kill a lot of zombies with guns or drive a car over them while trying to discover what really happened to this government black site facility.
	</description>
	
	<histories>
		<history>
		<header>NO MORE ROOM IN HELL</header>
		<text>Developed by indie gamedev Diego Giacomelli from Porto Alegre, RS, Brazil.</text>
		</history>		
  	</histories>

	<features>
		<feature>7 weapons</feature>
		<feature>destructible environment</feature>		
		<feature>drive a car</feature>		
		<feature>kill a lot of zombies</feature>		
	</features>

	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Trailer</name>
			<youtube>QKbeli5Jn0I</youtube>
		</trailer>
		<trailer>
			<name> S01E01 - Gameplay</name>
			<youtube>wKHpxzaaC2Y</youtube>
		</trailer>
		<trailer>
			<name>S01E03 - Gameplay</name>
			<youtube>n2A5SP1-xxk</youtube>
		</trailer>
	
	</trailers>

	<quotes>		
	</quotes>	

	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Diego Giacomelli</person>
			<role>Game designer, Unity developer and programmer</role>
		</credit>

		<credit>
			<person>Kenney</person>
			<role>Almost all sprites used in the game. https://kenney.nl</role>
		</credit>

		<credit>
			<person>Daniel HDR</person>
			<role>Soundtracks. https://www.danielhdr.com.br</role>
		</credit>

		<credit>
			<person>Peter Wayne</person>
			<role>Sound FX. https://www.gamemasteraudio.com</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>
</product>